Winning is all in the execution.
The Killer's Game is a action, comedy, thriller film directed by J.J. Perry.
When top hitman Joe Flood is diagnosed with a terminal illness, he decides to
take matters into his own hands – by taking a hit out on himself.
But when the very hitmen he hired also target his ex-girlfriend, he must fend off an army of
assassin colleagues and win back the love of his life before it's too late.
Joe Flood, played by Dave Bautista.
Maize Arnaud, played by Sofia Boutella.
Creighton Lovedahl, played by Terry Crews.
Antoinette, played by Pom Klementieff.
Max, played by Daniel Bernhardt.
Angus Mackenzie, played by Scott Adkins.
The Killer's Game is a 2024 American action thriller film directed by J.
Perry and written by Rand Ravich and James Coyne, based on the
1997 novel of the same name by Jay Bonansinga.
The film stars Dave Bautista, Sofia Boutella, Terry Crews,
Scott Adkins, Pom Klementieff, and Ben Kingsley.
The Killer's Game was released in the United States
by Lionsgate on September 13, 2024.
It received negative reviews and was a box-office bomb.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, hitman,
terminal illness, action comedy, comedy thriller.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.